Isn’t anyone gonna ask?
-You're gonna have sex with Penny.
-That's not what I was gonna tell you.
(Raj:)It's okay. I don't mind hearing
about your sex life.
(Raj:)It's his that bugs me.
(Leonard:)Guess who the university
is sending to Switzerland...
(Leonard:)...to attend a conference and see the
CERN Super Collider on February 14th?
Professor Norton. God knows why.
(Sheldon:)He hasn't published anything of note
since he won that Nobel Prize.
(Leonard:)Professor Norton can't make it.
He threw his back out climbing.
(Howard:)I heard he threw his back out
climbing on his girlfriend.
-Weather girl on Channel Two?
-That's the one.
(Leonard:)In any case,
they're asking me to fill in for him.
(Sheldon:)In Switzerland
or with the big-boobed weather girl?
(Leonard:)Switzerland.
And I get to bring a guest.
RAJESH: Oh, no way, dude!
-Oh, my God, this is incredible.
I'm so happy I'm not gonna question
their judgment in picking you.
I'm just gonna run home
and start packing.
Wait, why wouldn't you take Penny?
(Leonard:)I am taking Penny.
(Leonard:)Oh.
(Raj:)Then I anticipate an awkward situation
when you get home.